Amusement Park
Shikimori-san might like it??
Get a reservation!!!
Get gifts for the family
Eat this!!
Inuzuka-kun
Keep warm and go to bed early!!
Inuzuka-kun!!
Please Help
I'm going to an amusement park with
Shikimori-san next week. Suggestions...?
Yuu, hurry!
I can't believe every alarm clock in the
house broke on the day of his big test...
Yuu just bolted out of the house earlier.
Oh?
S-Sorry! Are you okay?!
I'm so late.
You're not hurt, are you?
Oh, no.
It's all right. I'm used to this.
Hand-Washing
Week
You were almost hit by a bike again?
Sorry.
You really need to be more careful.
You'll get yourself killed.
By the way, you have a
field trip coming up, don't you?
I'll be going too, so don't worry.
Exciting, isn't it?
Yes.
Five-minute break!
Izumi!
Observing again?
Yeah, since I got hurt the other day.
You got hurt again?
Well, that's Izumi for you.
Hey, wanna group up
with us for the field trip?
A-Are you sure? If I'm with you,
bad things might happen...
C'mon, it's fine! Don't worry about it!
Where should we go?
We can't miss that one place!
I hear ya!
Ow!
The heck?
It's huge!
I'm so sorry! Are you okay?!
Oh, yeah! No problem!
A falling teddy bear?
Never saw that coming.
I thought my neck was broken for a sec.
Man, that could've been bad. You okay?
That seriously hurt...
Unreal...
Yes. He isn't feeling well,
so I'd rather not send
him on the field trip.
Okay. Thank you very much.
Is my whole life just going
to be an endless loop of this?
God, are things ever going
to get any better for me?
If not, then please give me the strength
to endure all this pain and sadness.
If only a hero would appear before me...
Shikimori's Not Just a Cutie
Shikimori's
Not
Just
a
Cutie
Shikimori's
Not
Just
a
Cutie
Shikimori's
Not Just a Cutie
#11  Not Just a Cutie
Why did you come with me?
Got nothing else to do today.
I didn't ask you to come shopping.
Hey, I drove you here. No griping.
I never asked you to.
Aw, c'mon.
It's not so bad every now and then, is it?
Stop treating me like a child.
Well, you are still a child.
Excuse me?!
Way to prove my point.
I'm going to look at clothes.
What about you?
I'm gonna head where I wanna.
Drop me a line when you're done.
You're not even staying...
What? You sad?
You must be joking.
Ow, harsh.
Hmm... Should I go for cute or chic?
Which would be better?
So cool!
You're so cool!
I can't decide!
Huh?!
With the cultural festival and all,
we haven't had the chance...
This'll be our first date in so long!
It's been a while since we had
time to talk with just us, huh?
Yes, it has.
With the cultural and athletic festivals,
there was so much going on.
Yeah, plus I had that cold...
I'm just glad you feel better.
It made me happy when you
came over with Inuzuka-kun.
Huh? Er, d-did it?
Hey, let's go somewhere together again!
Sure, I'd love to!
Okay, let's decide right now.
Huh?
Oh, that's okay. We don't
need to decide right away.
I'm happy to go anywhere with you.
But... it's been so long since
it was just the two of us.
I want to talk with you more.
Bad idea...
Huh? What is?
This really is a bad idea.
Her heart is pounding
So, where shall we go next?
Well, things like spas
are popular right now.
A spa, huh? Sounds nice.
That would warm us right up.
Oh, this amusement park
commercial is really cool!
Really?
Let me just... Here.
"Off to Dreamland with the People You Love" Promo
What do you think? Should we—
We'll go.
You're sure, right?
Uh, yeah. I'm sure...
I didn't know you were so
interested in going there.
Uh, no, that's not...
A date like the one in that commercial...
I can't mess this up!
I couldn't decide on anything.
Aw, why not?
If you're free, you should
come to karaoke with us!
You're really good-looking!
Uh... er...
Aw, you're nervous! That's so cute!
I love it, I just love it!
You'll hang out with us, right?
Let's go.
Hey!
Who are you?
Sorry.
Well, damn. He had a cute girlfriend already.
Too bad.
So humiliating...
My kid sister had to bail me out!
The same one who used
to need me to hold her hand!
When was that, exactly?
Honestly, you're a lot shyer than you look.
Shut up. I'm just not great
with people I've never met.
Yeah, we call that being shy.
Are you sure you're not the one
who needs their hand held?
You are so not cute!
Thank you.
You can do anything you try, huh?
Not cute at all.
Are you... angry?
Nah. I'm better than you, anyway.
What? What's wrong?
Nothing.
Well, keep it up.
Micchan!
That was amazing!
You beat an older student!
And you only just started not long ago!
Yeah, really!
Hey, would you spar with me?
Me, too!
Mom, this is burnt.
It's fine. It's still just as healthy.
Starting tomorrow, you'll go
to the dojo by yourself.
Huh?
You can make it on your own now, can't you?
Yeah...
Once you've finished, wash the dishes.
Okay.
Are you going to continue with karate?
Huh?
It's unusual for you to start
something new on your own.
Fuji must have rubbed off on you.
Once you start something, no matter what it is,
there are choices you must make.
Including if you'll keep going.
I will.
I've made friends there,
and it makes people happy.
I see.
Then do your best.
Ow...
You okay?
You're a boy! Why'd you do that?!
It was her fault for spacing out.
You tripped her on purpose!
What? I don't need your false accusations.
You okay?
Y-Yeah...
Crap, that's Shikimori!
Stop it.
Shut up! Stay out of this!
There's the prince again!
How dashing!
What?
I said stop it.
Shikimori's scary! C'mon, run!
Karate girl!
Are you okay?
Yeah. Thanks, Micchan.
Seriously, Micchan, you're so cool!
Boys are nothing! You can just
beat them up with your karate!
Those boys totally have
a thing for Micchan.
Yeah, for sure!
Boys are just the worst.
I can't deal with boys
other than my brother.
I don't get all that "like" stuff at all.
You're a real sore loser, you know that?
Don't you get upset?
Nah. It's not like I lost.
Easy to say when you always win.
How many times have we had this talk?
Hey, that umbrella...
It's kinda weird.
Is it? Everybody has one.
No individuality at all...
Don't judge me over an umbrella.
They're popular,
so I just thought, "Why not?"
Huh...
I'm gonna quit karate.
Huh?
Out of the blue like that?
It's not, really.
But you won that last tournament.
I found something else I want to do.
What are you gonna do?
W-Well...
C'mon. Isn't there anything you wanna do?
You really have no individuality at all.
Don't just try to be like me or Mom.
Find what it is you really want
and make the choice for yourself.
Hey, Micchan...
Do you read manga?
Hmm... Not really.
Oh, okay...
I do read some of my brother's sometimes.
Really?!
Y-Yeah...
I just found a super
interesting one recently!
I'll lend it to you! Read it, okay?!
You must really like manga, Kayo-chan.
Okay. I'll check it out.
I can't reach it...
I guess...
I'm interested
in you.
Huh?!
The truth is...
I've always
been watching you.
Hug
I'll protect you.
Love is... incredible...
Shikimori wins!
Congrats on the win!
I can't believe you're going to nationals!
You really are strong, Shikimori-san!
Thanks.
Kanto Regional Karate Tournament
36th Annual Boys' & Girls' Championship
After winning this tournament,
your future's really promising!
Yeah! You'll kick butt at nationals, too!
No. Once I start high school...
I'm quitting karate!
What?!
South
Gymnasium
I've found what I want to do.
I want to be a cute girl.
I want to become a cutie
and fall in love with a kind, handsome boy.
I always felt comfortable
chasing after Nii-san or Mom.
I never worried about what to wear
or if my hair was out of place.
I just did what they told me to do.
That was enough.
What are you doing?
Losing weight!
Maybe the truth is that I don't
know what I want to be.
But...
It's okay if I'm not the real me.
I'll become the me I want to be.
Entrance Exam Site
Neat and tidy...
I hope my hair stayed put.
What should I do?
Is something the matter?
Oh, no, it's just...
My exam ticket got blown away,
and now it's stuck in this tree.
Oh...
It's pretty high up.
You're not getting anything down
from way up there without a ladder.
Is there time to get one?
Hmm... In any event,
I'll go get one. Wait right there.
I'll be right back.
Th-Thank you...
What am I gonna do?
I might be able to climb that high.
Huh?
Please hold this for me.
Uh... Wha...
Don't!
If you fall while climbing that,
you could get seriously hurt.
I'll be fine. I'm used
to doing things like this.
Still... it's dangerous.
So... I'd rather you didn't.
Wait, were you even listening?!
Darn it...
Wow, she's already that high up...
Here you go.
Th-Thank you.
No problem.
I haven't even started
high school yet and I blew it!
U-Um, you're not hurt
or anything, are you?
He must think I'm so unladylike now.
Hey, over here!
Long time no see!
Do I know you?
You're the girl who climbed the tree to get
my exam ticket when the wind caught it!
From when my high school
debut went up in smoke!
I-I'm glad you passed the exam
and got into this school.
H-Hey...
I've wanted to thank you all this time.
You really saved me that day!
Really, it was nothing.
Well, um, I'll be going now.
He must be so weirded out.
W-Wait!
I-I really have the worst luck.
If I'd climbed the tree that day,
a branch would've snapped,
the fall would've broken my leg,
and I never would've gotten in.
I've been unlucky since I was little.
All I've ever done is cause trouble
for the people around me.
So, um... I'm glad you're all right.
And I'm glad I got to see you again.
Wh-What am I even saying?!
Why...
Why is he smiling at me after
I did something so uncute?
Um, I just wanted to say I'm glad
I got to thank you in person!
I'm sorry! I'll go now!
Tell me your name.
I-It's Ijumi.
I swear, you're not cute at all.
You never were.
Shut up.
So? What'd you buy?
What?! You didn't buy anything?
Why'd you even come?!
Well...
I thought the problem was my clothes,
but I suddenly get the feeling it's not.
What're you talking about?
I don't know. I guess it's a
problem with me...
A mental thing, you mean?
Oh, to have it as easy as you do...
What?
This is what I mean. Normally
you'd stress over what to wear.
I don't even know why,
but you irk me so much.
I'll get Mom's advice on what to wear.
You baby.
Oh, shut up already.
How pretty!
But 5,000 yen?
Whatcha lookin' at?
I'd love to wear something
like this someday.
Are you old enough for that?
I'm seventeen now!
I feel like I could be stronger if I wore this.
You always need courage.
Is that how it works?
Look over here.
Onii-chan, where are you going?
Karate.
I'm...
I'm going with you.
Yeah, I still don't get it. Let's go.
What?
I went through a lot,
but I finally settled on what to wear.
What should
I wear with it
Try this one
News
See More
"Off to Dreamland with the peo
News
See More
"Off to Dreamland with the People You Love" Promo
I need to get ready...
Good luck
This is the one I was looking at!
I'm gonna hit the restroom. Wait here.
S-Sure.
Okay.
I'll do my best, Nii-san.
I'll leave your coat here.
Okay, thanks.
Well, I'm off!
SEE YOU~